You did it!
できたね!
I was able to have mass.
ミサできました
That's good!
いいじゃない!
She became a perfect maid.
完璧にメイドになりました
Perfect maid!
完璧メイドよ!
Look, look, at home.
見て見て、うちくんで
Look.
ほら
TRUE?
本当?
It suits you.
似合ってる
Does it suit you?
似合ってる?
cute!
かわいい!
Now I'm so excited.
これで、モエモエキュンって
Moe moe kyun, this is it.
モエモエキュンだよ、これもう
Moe moe...
モエモエ...
Moe moe kyun!
モエモエキュン!
I'm here.
いらっしゃいます
You're here, right?
いらっしゃいますだよね、もうね
It's already a shop, a shop.
もうお店だ、お店
Thank you, Master.
い ら っ しゃ い ませ、 ご主人様に
It's already a store, this is a store.
もうお店じゃん、これお店だ
Yes, it's already a shop.
そう、もうお店
It's a shop, this is it.
お店だよ、もうこれ
nice.
いいね
Let's drink, let's drink.
飲んじゃおう、飲んじゃおう
Let's have a drink.
飲 んじゃおう
Will Corey come in?
コーリー入りますか?
Enter Corey.
コーリー入ります
Does it suit you?
似合ってるかな?
It suits you so well.
そう似合ってるよ
Let's take a photo, then.
写真撮っていこう、それで
So, look, now you can do it in Cheki, too.
それで さ、ほら今、 チェキにもできるからさ、
Just take a picture with your cell phone and print it out on your instax.
ちょっと携帯撮ってさ、 チェキでプリントしてさ、
Come on, sign it later.
あとでさ、あれ、サインしてよ
Okay.
いいよ
It looks like a shop.
お店っぽくさ
delicious,
おいしい、
Eat more and drink more
ど んどん食べて、どんどん飲んで
hey.
ね
Okay, I'll take a picture of you while you're eating.
いい よ、食べてるところで撮るから
Oh, that's cute.
おー、かわいい
Now I'll check the best shot a little,
これでベストショットをちょっとチェキにするからさ、
Then sign it.
そしたらサインして
Super maid.
超メイド
I'm getting used to being a maid.
メイドさんになれてる
nice.
いいね
As expected from Akeba's con cafe place.
さすがアケバのコンカフェ場ですよ
This is a con cafe place.
コンカフェ場です
Welcome, Director.
いらっしゃいませ、ご指示様
That's nice.
いいねー
But for some reason, she's wearing undercoat.
でもなぜか、下毛をつけてますね
For some reason I don't wear them.
なぜか履いてない
For some reason, I noticed you were taking your clothes off earlier.
なぜか脱いじゃってるのさっきね
I need to take my clothes off.
なんか脱いじゃん
Follow me for a while.
ちょっと自分でついて
Isn't it okay?
いいんじゃない?
Good luck.
よきよき
Let's go back.
戻ろう
Oh no, you look fragile.
やばい、脆い見えてる
It looks fragile.
脆みえだ
I can see it.
見えちゃってる
No, it's embarrassing.
いやー、恥ずかしい
I haven't seen it directly.
俺、直接見てないからね
Because the camera just saw it.
カメラが見ただけだから
So cute.
めっちゃかわいい
That's good.
いいよね
Hey, can I take more pictures?
ちょっとじゃあ、 どんどん撮っていっていい?
Okay.
いいよー
I want to take the best shot
ベ ストショット撮りたいから
difference.
さ
That's nice.
いい ねー
Ah, that's nice.
あ、いいねそれ
It would be nice to see your legs after all.
やっぱり足見えるといいね
Hisa-chan has beautiful feet.
ひさちゃんは足きれいだからね
Seino.
せーの
yes.
はい
Ah, that's cute.
あ、それかわいい
Highest.
最高
Feels good.
いい感じ
Can you see a glimpse?
チラッとして見えますか?
A glimpse?
チラッと?
Down?
下?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Because of this angle.
この角度だからね
It's okay because you can't see it.
ちょうど見えないから大丈夫
I have to open my legs.
足開かなければ
I can't see it here.
ここ は見えない
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Well then, this way
じゃあ、 こっち
I also look at your feet.
も 足見ます
There really isn't.
本当に無いね
not at all.
全然
It hasn't been in since.
もっとから入ってないよね
From more?
もっとから?
Maybe I've forgotten how quick God is.
多分神様の経早さを忘れちゃったんだよね
A maid's work.
メイドの仕業
It's better without a maid.
メイドさん無い方がいいね
There's no maid.
メ イドさん無いの
The fairy lost it.
妖精さんが無くしてくれた
What about fairies?
妖精さんには?
The pants are cute, too.
パンツもかわいいけどやっぱ
That's amazing.
すごいね
Try expanding it yourself.
自分で広げちゃってみてよ
I'll check this out separately.
別にこれチェキンするから
Sign this later.
これサインして後で
I took a lot of pictures.
いっぱい撮っちゃった
いっぱい撮っちゃったよ
Amazing, these beautiful legs.
すごいじゃん、この綺麗な足
It's okay, you can drink this.
いいよ、これ飲んでもね
Shall we drink?
飲んじゃう?
Let's drink.
飲んじゃう
Wow, here we go.
うわー、いった
bitter.
苦い
Taste of spirit?
精神の味する?
strawberry milk.
イチゴミルク
Taste the spirit.
精神の味する
Taste of spirit?
精神の味する?
Where is your spirit?
精神のどこだんの?
be.
ある
What does it taste like?
どんな味?
The taste of milk.
ミルクの味
Is it about the same as the one I just drank?
今飲んだやつと一緒ぐらい?
It's finally here.
やっぱりやってきちゃったよ
Did you come after all?
やっぱりやってきた?
Have you ever had a drink with kits dressed like men?
男の格好付き合ったキットたちの飲んだことあるの?
be.
ある
Just a little bit
ちょっとこ
Tchi.
っち
I don't even have a brush attached.
ブ ラシも付けてないもんね
That's right, I just fell asleep.
そうなの、寝ちゃったさっき
Now that it has come all at once.
一気に来た今ので
Yeah, it came all at once.
うん、一気に来た
It's sweet.
甘いよ
Can I leave my camera behind?
カメラ置いちゃっていい?
yes.
そう
Already standing.
もう立ってる
Are you standing?
立ってるでしょ?
I was just taking a photo.
さっき写真撮ってるだけだって
He looks like that.
あんな格好してる
Don't you usually touch it yourself?
自分で普段触らない?
I touch it sometimes.
たまに触っちゃう
Don't you touch it sometimes?
た まに触らない?
Show it to your father.
お父さんに見せて
Do you do it like that sometimes?
そうやってやるの、たまに?
Yeah, I'll do it.
うん、やっちゃう
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
That's good.
いい じゃん
It's bad to take off your pants yourself.
パンツ自分で脱ぐのが悪いな
I took it off.
脱いちゃった
That's amazing.
すごいね
Where are you touching?
どこ触ってるの?
Cree.
クリー
I like Cree.
クリー好き
Do you like Cree?
クリー好きなの?
That's amazing, needles.
すごいね、針ね
Yeah.
うん
Get in
入れ
I'm chatting.
ちゃ ってる
You're putting it in, right?
入れてるよね、それね
It's wet.
濡れてる
There's a finger in it, too.
指も入ってるじゃん、それ
You put your middle finger in there, that's it.
中指入っちゃってるね、それね
It's in.
入 っちゃってる
I'm getting wet.
濡れちゃってる
It's bad for Isa-chan to be the only one with her panties off.
イサちゃんだけなんか、パンツ脱いでるの悪いからさ
I'll take my clothes off too.
俺も脱いちゃおう
Hey.
ねえ
Isn't it embarrassing to be alone?
一人だって恥ずかしいでしょ?
Yeah, it's embarrassing.
うん、恥ずかしい
You want me to take your clothes off, right?
脱いでほしいでしょ、一緒に
Yes, touch it yourself.
そう、触ってて、自分で
Here, here, here.
こ っちこっちこっち
Do you like it?
好きなの?
Yeah.
うん
I licked it, can you let me out?
舐めてちゃった、出してくれる?
Okay.
いいよ
TRUE?
本当?
Okay.
よ いしょ
Lick it.
舐めてよ
Lick it?
舐めて?
Yeah.
うん
It feels good.
気持ちいいそう
I like to lick it.
舐めるの好きなんだ
Yeah.
うん
I like licking.
舐めるの好き
Come on, try licking me from the side too.
ちょっとじゃあ、横からも舐めてみてよ
I've reached it here.
手届いちゃった、ここ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
I'll stand up for a while.
ちょっと立つからさ
What should I do, we ended up in this fight.
どうしよう、この喧嘩になっちゃった
I stood up.
立っちゃった
What should I do?
どうしよう
What should I do with this?
どうしよう、これ
Can I put something in there?
何か入れるかさ
I want to do one or the other.
どっちかしたい
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
Yeah.
うん
Both are good.
両 方いいな
I want to put it in my pussy.
マンコ入れてみたい
Shall I put it in?
入れちゃう?
I want to put it in.
入れてみたい
Don't tell me.
内緒だよ
Even if I put it in?
入れても?
Yeah.
うん
Okay,
よし、
Let's get it out.
出 しちゃおう
Let's come here.
こ っち来ちゃおう
oh yeah.
そうそう
amazing.
すごい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'm having a pussy.
マンコしてる
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels good.
気持ちいいよ
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
Usa-chan, did you become a hand?
うさちゃん、手になったの?
I wonder if it happened?
なったのかな?
I want to change the back.
後ろ変えたい
good?
いい?
Do you want to enter?
入れたい?
Ah, it's really included.
あー、すごい入ってる
Hands, look behind me.
手、後ろついてごらん
It feels good.
気 持ちいいね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It was crazy right now.
今、やばかった
It looked like it was going to come out.
出ちゃいそうだった
Are you curious? Well then.
気になっちゃうか、じゃあ
You'll get worked up.
気 を出しちゃうからね
I guess it felt good because I was doing it after all.
やっぱりやってるから、気持ちよかったんでしょうね
comfortably
気持ちよく
do not have.
ない
My stomach is full.
お 腹、いっぱい出ちゃった
Isn't your stomach flattened?
お腹、へこんだんじゃない?
It was a little dented.
ちょっとへこんだ
Because I exercised.
運動したから
Now I have to spend a lot of money at the store again.
これでまたお店でお金いっぱい使わないと
I'll be waiting.
待ってるね
I'll do some research again.
もう一回、ちょっと調べてくるわ